哦  你是在开什么玩笑
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
你听听斯宾塞刚才发的状态
Listen to spencer's latest status update.
“独自一人闲在家里无聊”  谁关心他啊
"just chilling at home." who cares?
显然你很关心啊
Apparently you do.
母亲啊  乱说  人家才没啊
Mom. No no, I do not.
我对我前男朋友的现状毫不在意
I could care less what my ex-boyfriend is up to.
看呐  他还没更改自己的状态唉
Oh, he hasn't even changed his online status yet.
上面还写着“热恋中”
It still says "in a relationship."
- 他就是无法忘怀我  - 呃  这个也许是他忘记了而已
- He just can't let me go.  - Well, maybe he forgot to change it.
呃  老妈  他怎么可能会忘啊  他一直都在线啊
Uh, mom, how could he forget? He's online all the time.
你怎么会对他如此的了解
And you know this how?
我每个小时就查看一次他的状态啊
I check his status every hour.
好吧  重要的是你已经克服了旧爱的羁绊
Well, the important thing is you've moved on.
盖比宝贝  今天下午你有玩伴陪你玩
Gabe honey, you have a playdate this afternoon.
- 我才没有呢  - 你有
- No, I don't.  - Yes, you do.
这条街上有人刚搬进来
A new family moved in down the street.
他们的孩子和你差不多大
And they have a son your age,
所以我计划了一番  这样你们可以一起玩玩
So I made plans for the two of you to get together.
哦  母亲大人啊  您犯的错容我一一道来
Oh, mom, let me explain where you went wrong.
我已经十一岁了  已经过了过家家的年龄了
I'm 11. I don't have "playdates" anymore.
哥老了  青春不再
I <i>hang.</i>
他叫奥斯丁  我觉得他会给你树立一个
His name is austin and I think he'll be.
很好的榜样的  他非常有修养有礼貌
A very good influence on you. He's very well-behaved.
你难道不知道我和有修养有礼貌之间是天生绝缘吗
You know that well-behaved and I are natural enemies.
你就不能说话客气一点吗
Could you just be nice?
好孩子  听话
Okay, be civil.
现在推辞为时已晚
It's too late to cancel.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
制作： line  后期：  kenix
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby, </i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好未来
<i>But I know your future is bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There is no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第一季第二十二集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E22 Teddy Rebounds
别告诉我水管坏了
Please don't be a plumbing problem.
Please don't be a plumbing problem!
谢谢参与  我们日后再联系
Thank you. We'll be in touch.
这是  这里又在搞什么幺蛾子
What is... what is going on?
我们在为乐队招聘新成员开试奏会呢
We're having auditions for a new band member.
咱乐队需要招能演奏更宽广音域的强人
P.J. And the vibe need a fuller sound
这样我们好有机会演出赚大钱
so we can start getting gigs.
你们所谓的宽广音域难道要靠迪吉里杜管帮忙吗
And that fuller sound is gonna come from a didgeridoo?
刚才那玩意叫这名啊
Is that what that thing is called?
好吧  问一下  你们的试奏会要持续多久
All right, look. How much longer are these auditions gonna go on?
- 再几个小时吧  - 我嘞个去
- For a few more hours.  - Oh man.
我真的要找地方自己住了
I really gotta get my own place.
下一位
Next.
谢谢支持  呃  麦克风你还是自己保留吧
Thanks. Uh, you can keep the microphone.
可以了  别弹了
Wait. Stop.
- 这也太差劲了  - 艾米特  别出言不逊
- That was awful.  - Emmett, don't be rude.
我很抱歉  但是你叫我说她演奏的很棒我可做不到
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna sugarcoat it,
即使她是我的祖母
Even if she is my grandma.
- 你的意下如何  - 这个吗  他演奏的很好
- What do you think?  - Well, he's pretty good,
但我觉得他的长相不够正点
But I'm not sure if he has the right <i>look.</i>
什么意思
What do you mean?
你看  我们俩都如此玉树临风
Well, you and me are so hot.
可是你看他..
And he's so...
好挫
Not.
这点我无法否认
I can't argue with that.
听着  吉米
Listen, jimmy.
我们俩要慎重考虑一下  然后再告知你结果
We're gonna think about it and let you know.
能不能尽快告诉我结果
Could you let me know soon?
因为我的哥哥这周末要开生日派对
'cause my brother's having a party this weekend.
他希望到时能有乐队现场演出  他愿意为此付钱的
And he wants live music. He's willing to pay.
哥们欢迎加入乐队
Welcome to the band.
嘿  奥斯丁  进来吧
Hey, austin. Come on in.
盖比宝贝  奥斯丁来了
Gabe honey, austin's here.
邓肯女士  你家好温馨啊
What a lovely home, mrs. Duncan.
看起来很清新整洁
So comfortable looking.
这么说混乱我听得好舒服啊
What a nice way of saying messy.
盖比  这位是奥斯丁
Gabe, this is austin.
- 兄台别来无恙 - 我身体又没事
- How do you do?  - How do I do what?
- 他是向你打招呼呢  - 你干嘛穿成那样
- He's saying hello.  - Why are you dressed like that?
这个吗  因为我不清楚我们要玩什么
Well, I wasn't sure what activities you had planned,
所以我就穿平时的便装出来了
So I settled on daytime casual.
老妈  不是吧
Really, mom?
你就让这小子和我一起度过这个下午吗
<i>This</i> is how you want me to spend my afternoon?
呃  你们好好玩啊  我上楼陪查莉去了
Well, you boys have fun. I'll be upstairs with charlie.
可怜的小孩身体不舒服
Poor little bby's not feeling well.
可怜的小盖比心情也很糟糕
Poor little gaby's not feeling so hot either.
那么现在准备玩什么  玩电脑游戏吗
What do you want to do, play video games?
-  呃  这个父母不准我玩  - 那么看电视呢
- Oh, I'm not allowed.  - Watch tv?
这周我看电视时间已经超过规定上限了
I've already exceeded my allotted one hour of the week.
- 那么去公园玩  - 抱歉我没抹防晒霜
- Go to the park?  - I'm not wearing sunscreen.
你觉得这样下去该咋整啊
How do <i>you</i> think this is going?
大家好
Hey, guys.
嗨
Hi.
我们素昧平生
I don't believe we've met.
泰迪  这位是奥斯丁  奥斯丁  这位是泰迪
Teddy, austin; Austin, teddy.
- 奥斯丁 很高兴见到你  - 见到你是我的荣幸
- Nice to meet you, austin.  - The pleasure is all mine.
哇  真是位小绅士哈
Well, aren't you a little gentleman?
她真有闭月羞花之色啊
She's glorious.
真是上天赐予之尤物啊
What an exquisite creature.
听好  我们得好好探讨一下
Look, we have to figure out how to get through this.
要不你别表现地那么怪异或者...
So either you stop being weird or...
唉  除此以外别无他法
Yeah, that's the only way.
所以说猴子就不该飞翔
that's why monkeys shouldn't fly
- 灰机  - 棒哦
- Planes!  - Yeah.
- 很好  - 好极了
- Yes!  - Yeah!
啊  这首歌真是正“惊”了
Yeah! That was awe-teous!
- 正“惊”  - 没错
- "awe-teous"?  - Yeah.
这叫正点和惊艳的结合体
I took "awesome" and mashed it with "righteous."
合起来就是正“惊”
"awe-teous."
伙计  用的词真好
Dude, I love that.
- 嘿  我能找点东西解渴么  - 没问题  厨房在楼上
- Hey, can I get something to drink? - Yeah, the kitchen's upstairs.
- 你觉得吉米这人如何  - 他"惊"顶了
- What do you think of jimmy?  - He's "gna-teous."
- 说啥  - 正惊和顶呱呱的结合体哈
- What? - I mashed "gnarly" and "awe-teous."
大哥  正惊已经是组合词了
"awe-teous" is already a mash-up.
随他吧
Just let him do it.
查莉宝贝  喝果汁吧
Charlie honey, drink your juice.
- 会让你一整天都好心情的  - 不不
- It'll make you feel better. - No no.
我觉得你不应该和我争辩
I don't think you should argue with me.
我知道的词可比你多多了
I know a lot more words.
抱歉  我能找点水喝么
May I have some water, please?
没问题  吉比  水马上就来
Sure, jimmy, coming right up.
哇  你实在太美丽可爱了
Well, aren't you a cutie-pie?
这种赞美我以前听过无数遍了
I'd be lying if I said I hadn't heard that before.
- 我是指宝宝  - 呃  好吧
- I... I meant the baby.  - Right. Huh.
哦  吉米  要是我我是不会离查莉太近的  她...
Oh, jimmy, I wouldn't get too close to charlie. She's...
...生病了
...Sick.
天哪
Whoa.
她把我喷的一脸鼻涕
She blasted me with snot.
不过这恰巧是我上个乐队的名字哎
Which was also the name of my last band.
奥斯丁来了  告诉他我不在家
It's austin. Tell him I'm not here.
抱歉  奥斯丁  盖比不在家
Sorry, austin, gabe's not here.
他藏在毛毯下面了
He's hiding under that blanket.
事实上吗  我来是为了见你的
Actually, I came to see you.
- 不是吧  - 哇  事情发展地越来越有戏剧化了
- You did?  - Well, this just got interesting.
我给你带了点礼物
I brought you some presents.
一盆非洲兰花  我亲手栽种的
An african orchid. I cultivate them myself.
我还特意为你制作了这个香皂
I also made you some soap.
谢谢
Thank you.
恰好我正缺少兰花和香皂唉
I was running low on orchids and soap.
还有别的么
Anything else?
我还想问你一些问题
I also wanted to ask you something.
- 好吧  - 你愿意和我一起出去吗
- Okay.  - Will you go with me?
去哪里
Go with you where?
我是在问你愿意做我女友吗
I'm asking you to be my girlfriend.
打住  我很抱歉  你在说什么
Wait. I... I'm sorry, what?
我都要十六岁了  而你才十一而已
I'm almost 16 and you're 11.
是十一岁半
And a half.
我想现在这里有很大的问题亟待解决
I believe there's a question on the table.
泰迪  爱情是不受年龄所限制的
Teddy, love knows no age.
但是身高很有影响
But it does know height.
奥斯丁  我有点受宠若惊  但是人家刚刚才和别人分手
Austin, I'm flattered, but I just came out of a relationship.
“我恋爱了  让我们看看爱对我们是否足够”
"I have loved, let us see if that's all."
出自E.E.康明斯
E.E. Cummings.
注：E.E.Cummings-美国20世纪现代主义实验派诗人
“我完全没有兴趣”  出自TR邓肯
"I'm not interested." t.R. Duncan.
你在语言上拒绝了我  可是你的眼神却透露了另一种讯息
Your words say one thing, but your eyes say another.
好吧  看看我的手
Okay. Focus on my hands.
我要友好的请你出去了
They're pushing you out the door.
一切才刚开始  我会回来的
This is not over. I shall return!
告诉你  现在他让我感兴趣了
You know, he's growing on me.
- 我收到你的短信了  有什么坏消息  - 吉米病倒了
- I got your message. What's the bad news? - Jimmy's sick.
查莉打了他一脸喷嚏
Charlie sneezed on him.
现在他没办法在周末和我们一起演出了
Now he can't make the gig this weekend.
- 哎呦哎  这真是不可置"惊"...  -  别搞这套了
- Man, that's "awf-able." - Stop that!
兄弟  我们必须尽快找到乐队的贝斯手
Dude, we have got to find a new bass player and fast.
- 去哪里找啊  - 我也说不好
- But where? - I don't know.
- 老爸  - 嘿
- Dad?  - Hey.
哦  抱歉
Oh sorry.
我看到这些乐器后就情不自禁了
I saw it here. I couldn't resist.
- 你怎么会弹这些的  - 我在上高中的时候
- How'd you learn to do that?  - When I was in high school,
那时我也自己组了个乐队  鲍勃邓肯体验乐队
I had my own band... the bob duncan experience.
你竟然玩过乐队  怎么我一点也不知道啊
You were in a band? How come I never knew that?
因为每当我想谈谈我以前的故事
Because whenever I start a story.
"想当年我在高中的时候"  你就充耳不闻
With "when I was in high school," you zone out.
我很抱歉  你刚才在说啥
I'm sorry. What?
那个  邓肯叔  你真是我们乐队的救星
Well, mr. D. , you are the answers to our prayers.
你愿意参与...
How would you like...
乐队会议
Band meeting.
还乐队会议啊
Band meeting?
大事不妙
That's not good.
当年我被鲍勃邓肯体验乐队开除之前
That's how I got thrown out.
他们也开了类似的会议
Of the bob duncan experience.
艾米特  我可不想成为和老爸在一个乐队的衰哥
Emmett, I don't want to be the loser who's in a band with his dad.
孩子们  说话小声些
A little quieter, guys.
我清楚他年龄不小了
I know he's old,
可是事到如今我们还有别的选择吗
But what choice do we have?
你们说的我可听的一清二楚哦
Still hearing it.
我想你说的很有道理
I guess you're right.
老爸
Dad...
你想和我们一起参与表演吗
Do you want to do the gig with us?
好极了  乐队生涯继续了
Yes! The experience continues!
我王者归来了
I'm back!
就只能参与一场演出
For one gig only.
“你是我生命中不灭的光芒”  奥斯丁
"you are the light of my life. Austin.
附注  这句话不适合运用不通风的环境
P.S., not to be used in non-ventilated areas."
好极了  喜欢姐的小屁孩
Yep, that's my special fella.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
那个  斯宾塞  啊
Okay. Spencer, uh,
说起来有点不好意思  可是我有话要对你说
This is awkward, but I have to tell you something.
- 没问题  说吧  - 那个  我看到了你的网络状态
- Sure, what is it?  - Well, I heard your online status.
上面写着你仍在热恋中
Says you're in a relationship...
这是有人告诉我的  我忘记是谁说的了
Somebody told me, I don't remember who...
所以说呢  你应该更新一下状态吧
So you should probably change that.
- 我只是说说而已  - 事实上  我是改过了
- I'm just saying.  - Actually, I did change it.
- 可是后面又改回来了  - 呃  好吧
- And then I changed it back. - Huh. Okay look,
我知道你对我余情未了
I know you still have feelings for me.
我很理解  我对别人有着超乎寻常的影响力
I get it. I have that effect on people.
可是  是时候放下旧情了  好吧
But really, it's time to move on, okay?
泰迪  我写的状态和你无关
Teddy, my status isn't about you.
我  哦
I... oh.
我说的那位是妮可尔  我们约会过几次
Her name's nicole. We've had a few dates.
她不在我们学校上学
She doesn't go to our school.
呃  那个  你真幸运
Well, that's...that's good for you.
呃  我的意思是我们两个都很幸运
I mean it's good for both of us, actually,
因为我也恋爱了
Because I'm also in a relationship.
- 你真的  - 没错
- You are?  - Yes.
- 不错嘛  你的情郎是谁  - 呃  他叫...
- Cool. Who is it?  - Uh, austin...
奥斯丁
Is his name.
奥斯丁也没有在我们学校上课
Austin doesn't go to our school.
他
He...
不过送我了这根大蜡烛  无所谓了
Got me this candle. Whatever.
啊  这礼物很不错
Ah. That's nice.
没错  他就是那么贴心靠谱
Yeah, he's thoughtful like that.
啊  是妮可尔打来的
Ah. It's nicole.
- 我得接一下电话  - 没问题  接去吧
- I should probably take this.  - Oh sure. Go for it.
我也得和奥斯丁通个话
I have to call austin anyway...
哪天他的年龄到可以拥有手机的时候
Once he's old enough to have a phone.
嘿  泰... 哦
Hey, te... oh.
别告诉我你还对斯宾塞恋恋不舍
Please tell me you're not still obsessing about spencer.
才不对呢  我现在对一位叫妮可尔的小妞很感兴趣
No no, I'm obsessing about some girl named nicole.
斯宾塞假定的约会对象
Who he's supposedly dating.
但是我觉得这个人压根就不存在
But I don't think she exists.
我刚才搜过了他人人上的四百五十二名好友
I just scrolled through all 452 of his friends.
根本就没有一个叫妮可尔的
And there's not one nicole.
你觉得他会为了惹怒你
You think he made up a fake girlfriend.
而去瞎编自己有个女朋友吗
Just to get a rise out of you?
哦  这真是既可悲又可怜啊
Oh, that is sad and pathetic.
这个吗  在某些特定场合下
Well, in certain situations.
这么做是可以理解的
It's understandable.
你编造的男朋友叫什么
What's your fake boyfriend's name?
奥斯丁
Austin.
- 哦  泰迪  - 我慌了神了
- Oh teddy.  - I panicked!
至少他还是个真实存在的男人啊
At least he's a real guy.
这首曲子献给你  我的挚爱
<i>For you, my love!</i>
这不会是琵琶曲吧
Is that the lute?
哦  我最喜欢琵琶了
Oh, I love the lute.
抱歉  奥斯丁  你出现的时机可不太对
Sorry, austin. Now's not a good time.
泰迪  和我一起出去吧
Teddy, go out with me.
- 不  - 那么我将会倾囊我所有的乐器
- No. - Then I will continue to serenade you.
来为你演奏一曲曲动人的小夜曲
With every instrument at my disposal.
但是有一点你必须清楚
But you should know.
我父亲可是开乐器行的
My father owns a music store.
那么我要怎么做你才可以离开这里
So what's it gonna take to make you go away?
一次约会即可
One date.
好吧  早死早超生
Okay, fine. Let's get this over with.
现在可不行  我还没打扮好唉
Well, not now. I'm not dressed.
周六下午我会来见你
I shall return Saturday afternoon.
- 一点如何  佳人  - 随你便了
- Shall we say 1:00-ish?  - Say whatever you want.
我们的关系到三点整了断
Our relationship ends at 3:00-ish.
我先祝你早上好
Until then I bid you a gentle good morrow.
棒极了
<i>Yahoo!</i>
老爸  来啊  我们看看你的形象
Dad! Come on, let's have a look at you.
怎么样  看看我
Huh? Look at that.
我这么打扮像青少年吗
Can I pass for a teenager?
当然可以
Absolutely.
只要你不被光直射到
Just stay out of direct light...
或者照到
Or any light.
- 那不会是青春痘吧  - 答对了  我自己化妆的
- Is that a zit?  - Yep, drew that on myself.
这样让我更加年轻有活力  不是吗
Makes me look younger, huh?
老爸  青春痘可表示压力很大啊
Ugh. Putting a lot of pressure on one little zit, dad.
好吧  老爸
Okay. Dad.
- 我们再过一遍  - 嗷  好吧
- Let's go over it one more time.  - Oh, all right.
我的名字叫小布  我在北中上学
My name is bo. I go to north high.
如果有人问起的我的话  我的身体状况异于常人
And, if anybody asks, I have a bizarre medical condition.
- 让我看上去年龄偏大  - 什么病啊
- That makes me look older.  - Called?
老年综合征
Old-man-itus.
很好
We're good.
哦  老公
Oh, honey.
今晚想和一位青少年出去疯么
Want to go out with a teenager tonight?
有那个青春痘可不行
Not with that zit.
这就是我们的约会吗
This is our date?
竟然是你六岁堂妹的生日晚会
Your six-year-old cousin's birthday party?
我不能不带女伴出席啊
I couldn't show up without a date.
否则我就糗大了
That would be embarrassing.
我们不想这里还有别人出糗
We wouldn't want anyone here to be embarrassed.
不是那里  我特意准备了我们俩的专属座位
Oh, no, I've arranged a <i>private</i> table for us.
真浪漫啊
How romantic.
我给了小丑几美刀
I slipped the clown a few dollars.
他很快就会来
He'll be by shortly.
拜托  用心点摇好不好
Come on, swing like you mean it!
等到我们可以离开这里时  她都要七岁了
She's gonna be seven by the time we get out of here.
不会花那么长时间的
It won't take that long.
皮纳塔游戏后  我们享受一下生日蛋糕
After the pinata, we have cake.
- 然后亲个小嘴  一切结束  - 你在说啥
- Then we kiss and it's over.  - What did you say?
我们享受生日蛋糕
We have cake.
呃  到你了
Uh, it's your turn.
啊  我要上了
Ah. Let's do this.
女孩们  打开包吧  这道绚丽的彩虹马上就要成为历史了
Open your bags, girls. This pretty rainbow's going down.
没错  这才是我想要的效果  哇
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about! Whoo!
- 泰迪吗  - 哦 斯宾塞
- Teddy?  - Oh! Spencer.
还真是你啊  你画老虎的妆吗
That is you, uh, tiger.
- 兄台别来无恙  - 哦  天哪
- How do you do?  - Oh my gosh.
我身体又没事
How do I do what?
- 我叫奥斯丁  - 这位就是你所说的奥斯丁吗
- I'm austin.  - This is austin?
就是那位和你拍拖的
The guy you're in a relationship with?
这个吗  这只是我们第一次约会而已的
Well, it's just our first date.
我们要一步一步来
We're taking things slow.
呃  那么我先走了  妮可尔还在那里等我呢
Um, well, I should go. Nicole's waiting for me.
- 很高兴见到你  - 先生  我也很高兴见到你
- It was nice to meet you.  - And you, sir.
你好么
Are you okay?
不大好
Not really.
那位是我的前任男友
That was my ex-boyfriend.
- 哦  - 他现在在那里陪妮可尔
- Oh. - He's here with nicole,
不仅漂亮而且算是货真价实的女友
Who is pretty and <i>real.</i>
而你却在和一位十一岁少年厮混
And you're here with an 11-year-old.
差不多吧
Pretty much.
这么说吧  泰迪
Well, you know, teddy,
也许我年龄仅仅只有十一
I may be only 11,
但我足以了解你需要某人的关爱
But I'm old enough to know you deserve someone.
需要某人欣赏你的美丽
Who will appreciate how wonderful you are.
而我觉得  斯宾塞鬼才配得上你
And for your information, spencer ain't it.
- 你刚才不会说“鬼”了吧  - 听听我啊
- Did you just say "ain't"?  - Listen to me.
我热情似火  已经把规范用语置之度外了
I'm so passionate, I'm throwing grammar to the wind.
谢了  奥斯丁
Yeah thanks, austin.
告诉你  作为第一次约会
And you know, as first dates go,
目前还不算很糟糕
This wasn't all that bad.
斯拉皮  现在不是时候
Not now, slappy.
不论怎么说  你真的
Anyway, you really...
你也应有别人的爱抚
You deserve somebody great too.
我的意思是  一位聪明的
I mean, somebody who's smart.
善解人意的  十一岁女生
Kind and, well, 11.
我们不如把糖果包带走  迅速亲一下
Shall we grab our goody bags, quick kiss.
- 然后离开这里  - 你说啥
- And get out of here?  - What did you say?
我是说我们把糖果包带走吧
I said let's grab our goody bags.
所以说猴子不应该飞翔
that's why monkeys shouldn't fly
灰机
planes!
太糟了  我们完全失败了
This is awful. We're totally bombing.
他们根本不往我们这里瞟两眼
They're not even paying attention to us.
听着  伙计们  冷静
All right, guys. Calm down.
如果说我从鲍勃·邓肯体验乐队里学到了什么的话
If there's anything I learned from the bob duncan experience,
那就是如果你想吸引别人的注意的话
It's that if you want to get people to notice you,
- 你必须制造噱头让别人注意  - 这该怎么做
- You give them something to notice.  - How do you do that?
乐队会议  听着  伙计  下面按我说得来
Band meeting. Okay, guys, follow my lead.
观众们一定会为此疯狂的
This crowd's about to get <i>fired</i> up.
我的嘴巴熊熊热火燃烧
my mouth is on fire!
my mouth isn fire!
我的嘴巴熊熊热火燃烧
my mouth is on fire!
燃烧吧  青春
fire!
那个  查莉
Well, charlie,
多亏了那位行为怪异的正太奥斯丁
Thanks to a strange little dude named austin,
我想我终于可以忘记斯宾塞了
I think I'm finally over spencer.
事实上  我马上就要把他从好友列表中删除了
In fact, I'm about to defriend him right now.
喔  结束了
Whoo! Moving on.
感觉真棒
Feel good.
哦  看起来我收到了来自...
Ooh, looks like I have an email from...
奥斯丁的邮件
Austin.
哦  他竟然把我画老虎妆的照片
Oh, he posted the teddy the tiger pictures.
发的全因特网都是
All over the internet.
祝我好运  查莉
Wish me good luck, charlie.
喔   这是怎么了
Whoa! What happened?
老爸表演喷火了  真的太壮观了
Dad breathed fire. It was <i>so</i> awesome...
仅第一次而言
The first time.
第二次喷火的时候出了点故障
The second time there were some problems.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
明天早上我就去乐器行
Tomorrow morning I'll go down to the music store.
给吉米买个新贝斯
And get jimmy a new bass,
然后去木材房
Then go over to the lumber yard.
给吉米的父母买个演出平台
And get jimmy's parents a new deck.
打住  老爸  你不会在PJ的乐队里演出了吧
Wait. Dad, you played in p.J.'s band?
- 我还不懂你对音乐有兴趣啊  - 我当然有了
- I didn't know you were into music.- Of course I am.
当我还在高中的时候  我也有自己的乐队
When I was in high school, I had my own band.
我很抱歉  你说啥
I'm sorry, what?
我真的要找地方自己住了
I really got to get my own place.
嘿
Hey!
看好啦  这乐器不劲爆吗
Look at that. Ain't she a beauty?
你不是已经给吉米赔了一架贝斯了吗
I thought you already bought jimmy a bass.
- 这可是我买给自己的  - 老爸  呃
- This is for me.  - Dad, um,
我想之前我们已经说好了
I thought we made it pretty clear.
你加入乐队仅此一次而已
You being in the band was just a one-time thing.
- 对此我很抱歉  - 没事
- I'm sorry.  - I'm not.
我现在也有自己的乐队了
I've got my own band now.
这样不行
All right. Okay whoa.
打住  停一下  停停停
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Stop stop stop.
我们再来一遍  好吧
Let's try it again, all right?
这次风琴的音调低一点
Let's bring the accordion down a little bit.
你弹奏的部分多一点  你就省省吧
A little more from you. A little less from you.
至于艾米特的奶奶吗
And as for emmett's grandma...
你演奏的很好
You sound great.
好的  听好了  从头再来一遍  好吗  倒数三
Alright, listen. One more time from the top. Ok? On 3...
嘿  鼓手  专心点  我说过了“倒数三”
Hey, drummer, come on. I said "On three".
哦  好吧  你现在...还数不到三
Oh that's right, you... You can't count to three yet.